Timothy Cocores

(415) 640-0398 | timothycocores@gmail.com

Objective

Several years in Technical Support and Operations, highly skilled in troubleshooting problems and providing assistance to customers or employees. Strong oral/written communicator, able to communicate answers effectively. Also able to change roles at the drop of a hat. Passionate in exceeding expectations and continuous learning to improve industry knowledge and experience.

Experience

Refinery29 | Support Engineer | 2015- Present

- Support for over 400 employees
- Responsible for imaging computers and new user set up
- Provide user support, software, hardware, and network assistance for office
- Program installation and licensing
- Troubleshooting computer related issues in a mostly Mac heavy environment.
- Addressing and fixing issues connecting to companies' local server.
- Working with tech team to code internal company directory.

Squarespace | Customer Operations Shift Lead | 2014-2015

- Lead and coached a subset of the customer care team to help customers get a great experience.
- Responsible for the daily activities of the team, including e-mail, live chat and other supporting functions (quality, training, escalations)
- Creation of bug reports that get sent to the engineering team
- Answering questions in main chat for my team as well as other teams

Squarespace | Customer Operations | 2013-2014

- Focus on helping our customers achieve success with our products
- Respond quickly to customer-submitted email requests and live chats
- Troubleshoot and guide customers through website setup, including identifying system and site-specific website issues.
- Helping customers via live chat to help fix site and resolve issues.

HeyBubble INC. | Help Desk Administrator | 2012-2013

- Set up workstations for new hires, including imaging computers, software/hardware installs
- Assist in the implementation of network changes.
- Document, track and monitor issues via ticket tracking system (JIRA) to ensure a timely resolution
- Work with engineering team to get the website designed
- Create and approve designs of the website for user experience and interface.

Education

Academy of Art University | San Francisco, CA 2008 - 2011

Major: Advertising

University of Missouri St. Louis 2012 - 2015

Major: Communications

Skills

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Adobe Illustrator (CS5) Adobe PhotoShop (CS5), Adobe In-Design (CS5), Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Premiere Pro, Final Cut Pro X, Tumblr, Instagram, Twitter, desk.com ticket system, GitHub VPN setup, Trello, Adept in Mac, Windows, iOS, Android. HTML 5, CSS 3, Javascript, Jquery, and Bootstrap,